you
The wind has drove beyond the trees
A sudden calm upon the seas
We watched the lightning strike the ground
But now there is no other sound
The broken glass is swept away
To leave us in the light of day And we are walking
in the silent storm
Waiting for the wear to keep us warm
The empty space is just a shape we leave behind A
quiet place for us to finally find
In the silence
You fold the papers, close the door
We don't need answers anymore
The orchestra has gone to sleep
And gave us promises to keep
We cross the ocean in the dark
To rescue one remaining spa And we are walking in
the silent storm
Waiting for the weather to keep us warm
The empty space is just a shape we leave behind A
quiet place for us to finally find
In the silent storm
The true light bleeps It always bleeps We wake up
from the shattered dreams
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
The silent storm